

CONTACT

- **2** 254-652-2689
- Story City, IA

<u>ACHIEVEMENTS</u>

- · ISU Dean's List
- U.S. Navy Conduct Award
- University Course Framework Project
- · Pokemon ASCII Project

SOFT SKILLS

- Creativity
- Resilience
- · Continuous Learning
- Adaptability
- · Time Management
- Prioritization
- Organization
- Problem Solving
- Collaboration
- Resourcefulness
- Self-Sufficient
- Mentoring
- Curiosity

PORTFOLIO

Scan here or visit jacobisu.github.io/Portfolio



JACOB SMITH

Computer Scientist · Navy Veteran

My experiences in life have brought me to this exciting moment! I am a highly motivated individual with a deep passion for computer science. As a Navy veteran, I bring a unique set of skills in task completion and problem-solving. Paired with my Bachelor of Science, I am ready to learn more, build more, and master the challenges ahead of me.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science • Computer Science

Iowa State University · 3.3 GPA · August 2020 - May 2024

- Object-Oriented Programming
- · Data Structures & Algorithms
- Software Development
- · User Interface & User Experience
- Computer Graphics
- · Design & Analysis Of Algorithms
- · Computer Architecture & Machine-Level Programming
- Advanced Programming Techniques
- Network Protocols & Security
- Principles Of Programming Languages
- · Operating Systems
- · Theory Of Computing
- Principles Of Artificial Intelligence
- Software Testing

EXPERIENCE

Water Treatment Operator

City Of Amarillo, TX · November 2017 - April 2020

- Laboratory testing to ensure water quality
- · Record keeping of plant operations
- · Troubleshooting and resolving operational issues

Avionics Technician

U.S. Navy · May 2013 - May 2017

- Maintaining aircraft electrical systems & components
- · Executing shore duty & dry dock operations
- · Honorably discharged after four years of service

TECHNICAL SKILLS

JavaC/C++C#PythonSQLJavaScriptHTML/CSSGit/GitHubVisual Studio CodeEclipseIntelliJUnityAndroid StudioUnixReactNodeMongoDBMySQLPowershellBashXMLMaven

VirtualBox Make WebGL Kotlin LEGv8